▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 决赛
高芙 6-2 6-4 佩古拉 · 赛后捧杯致辞
Well, first I want to say congrats to Coco
首先我想恭喜高芙
and her team.
和她的团队。
Gosh, you were like a backboard today.
天呐，你就是一堵回球墙。
It was not fun to play against.
打你真的很难受。
I didn't even think I played bad.
我都不觉得自己打得差，
I just think you played
只是觉得你
a really, really high level.
发挥得实在太出色了。
So, congrats.
所以，恭喜你。
Uh
呃，
Amazing momentum headed
士气这么好，
into the US Open.
正好冲着美网去。
And obviously, I mean, we know each other
而且，我们彼此太了解了，
so well.
太熟悉了。
I I I can't really see you.
我都看不清你人在哪儿。
We know each other so well,
我们真的太了解彼此，
and I have so much respect for you.
而且我非常尊敬你。
So, I just enjoy being able to share the court
能和你同场竞技，
with you, practice with you,
一起训练，
be at these tournaments with you.
一起打这些赛事，我很享受。
For when you first came on tour,
从你刚上巡回赛那会儿起，
it's it's been a wild ride, at least
这段旅程一直很疯狂，
for the amount that I have seen you.
至少我看着你走过来是这样。
So, it's amazing.
真的很了不起。
Congrats to you and your team,
恭喜你和你的团队，
and all the best going forward.
祝你未来一切顺利。
Thank you.
谢谢。
I'm a little upset I have two of these now.
我现在有点郁闷，第二次了。
I wanted the bigger one, but that's okay.
我想要更大的那个，没事。
It's still a pretty trophy.
这个也很漂亮。
And next I want to thank
接下来我想谢谢
my team that's here with me this week.
这周一直陪着我的团队。
Mark Knowles, Spencer,
马克·诺尔斯、斯宾塞，
Seba, thank you guys
还有塞巴，谢谢你们
for supporting me this week.
这一周的支持。
We had a fun 12 days, or however long
这十二天，或者说
it's been, a couple weeks together.
这几周我们相处，很开心。
So, it's been a lot of fun.
真的很有意思。
I think I've stressed you guys out a lot
这几场比赛我肯定没少让你们
over the last few matches.
操心。
So, thanks for sticking it with me.
谢谢你们一直陪着我扛过来。
And to Mark and John,
还有马克和约翰，
my other coach and my trainer back home,
我另一位教练和体能师，
my husband, my family, my dogs
我的丈夫、家人和狗狗们，
that were actually here for a brief period
它们也来过这儿一小段时间，
and got to support me.
陪我加油。
But, thanks to everyone back home that's
也谢谢家里
been cheering me on.
一直为我加油的每一个人。
It's been an awesome 2 weeks
这两周真的很棒，
and an honor to be back in the final here.
能再打进决赛，是种荣幸。
Next, I want to thank thank you
接下来我想谢谢
to Credit One, to Kelly and Ben Navarro.
谢谢 Credit One、凯莉和本。
You guys have been so so great to me,
你们对我一直特别好，
not only here, but also in Charleston
不只是在这儿，在查尔斯顿
when I come to play your event.
我去打你们那站比赛也一样。
So, thank you guys for just investing
谢谢你们
so much into tennis and growing
在网球上投入这么多，
this sport everywhere throughout
把这项运动
the country.
带到全国各地。
It's amazing.
真的很了不起。
Thanks to Bob.
谢谢鲍勃。
I I think we all love you so much.
我们都特别喜欢你。
So, like, you're awesome.
你真的很棒。
All the players love being around you.
所有球员都喜欢有你在身边。
Thanks for getting me
谢谢你
an espresso last minute.
临时给我弄了一杯浓缩咖啡。
Yeah, I think I needed another one,
我确实还需要再来一杯，
but it's okay.
不过没关系。
And thanks Pam and everyone out
也谢谢帕姆和所有
that puts on this event, the volunteers.
为这场赛事付出的志愿者。
I mean,
说真的，
I think the volunteers here are so nice,
这儿的志愿者都特别好，
all the workers, everyone from the ball kids
所有工作人员，从捡球的孩子
to the people checking our badges
到检查我们证件的人，
and getting the cars and everything.
还有安排用车的人。
You guys are amazing.
你们都太棒了。
And yeah, it makes it so much fun
这让打球
to play here, really.
在这儿打球很有意思，真的。
I mean, I do I love playing here.
我是真的很喜欢在这儿打球。
It's just It's such a cozy kind
这里有一种
of warm-hearted feeling playing tennis here
很温馨的感觉，
in Cincinnati, so I love it.
在辛辛那提打球我很喜欢。
And last but not least, thank you
最后同样重要的是，谢谢
so much to the fans that come out.
所有到场的球迷。
You guys are some of the best best fans
你们是我们遇到过
that we have.
最好的球迷之一。
Truly, you really are.
真心的，你们真的是。
I I think I sign more autographs here
我觉得我在这儿签的名
than anywhere else.
比其他任何地方都多。
So, it's it's a lot of fun for us.
这对我们来说真的很有意思。
And just thank you so much for coming out
谢谢你们
and supporting us.
到场支持我们。
So, thank you guys.
谢谢大家。
Let's
我们……